Oh my oh my
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh oh
Oh my, oh my
Oh my oh my
uh
Uh, uh, I went down to the first floor.
Taraman
If you come, you will be the last customer today. Yes.
Welcome
Welcome to the leader
so are you ready
for the consultation
yeah yeah
this one should i follow you yes
what brings you here
for the makeup
i want to hear your story
well i know
that the like
Korean beauty is really popular
and i wanted
to learn a little bit more about it
yeah um i work with some korean
models
so i usually go in looking for
the professional
alright okay
hi i'm tara lanaway
i'm actually gonna be fifty two
i'm living in New York city i'm
a model agent
at an agency in New York here
called the society management
i've probably been working with
male models for probably about
fifteen twenty years now almost
um some
of the models
i work with are from Korea
and they've brought back
some beauty products as gifts
sometimes
but i don't know a lot about k
beauty so this was like my way
of getting to kind of
see what it's like
and try it out
obviously
i want to look glowy and pretty
and younger
everybody does
you are so beautiful nice to meet you nice to meet you your picture is very nice
thank you what do you like
hairstyle today
what i'm open
to hearing
what you think would look nice
like and what suits my face or
that's okay okay
my boyfriend is um
is in town
and so we're gonna go for dinner
tonight
he's just blown in
um from Canada
he's from Canada yeah oh my god
he's from Canada
yeah i'm originally from canada
i've been living in new york for
alright
oh i think i moved here in 2012
i've been living here
for a while
what do you do
I work at a modeling agency
ah modeling agency
yeah i represent male models
all right
so what do i look like
you you're pretty handsome guy
Really Korea, what should the CEO say now?
handsome
What is Guy? It's not me.
I don’t want to do it now, First Handsome
Is it me? Who is first?
He's a handsome guy.
Why are you looking so straight
who
Ouch to someone who who who who
누구
아
어디 어디
아 진짜
you busy right now
you're getting bored
are you getting bored
i have a lot of work to do
i have a lot of work to do okay
i'm a research scientist
so i do a lot of writing
so what do you do now
what do you do
what do i do yeah
i'm a professor and
a professor
i did medicine Edison
alright alright yeah
so when are you going back
tomorrow tomorrow
so is this your last dinner
that was her last week
actually so
okay so
that's cool so yeah it's nice
i remember
when you go to a conference they
usually have
a night of entertainment
oh yeah
and they did an entertainment
show i think that
they had like all these
knives and chopping
and i think they were like
ah it is nanta yes is it
have you seen it yes oh so i
i was the volunteer so they they
i remember that they
they pulled me up on stage
a couple of volunteers
so these try it
yeah i used to be a juggler
i used to be
a juggler so i oh did you yeah
so that was my before
being a doctor i was a juggler
really
that's why before
being a doctor i was a
checkler really
like that was my job to get to
medical school
to professor
i get paid pretty good money
to do that okay
yeah so how many
bowls can you juggle
well
uh it's five six six yeah
serious
i can juggle like three three
but you need
sometimes
a little bit of weight
it always helps
ah let me find let me
let me have a look
can you can you do this no
not again
what's that
ah yeah right
There's nothing
nothing to try
what about this
sanitizer
nope
ah i wanna see
Ah se
It's here It's here It's here
here it is here here
Ah hehe what is it
What what what what what
5 nice
you know what it's really
good it's like apple
ah yeah right orange
like Mandarin those are good
oh it's it's quite
oh see yeah is it good
see yeah is it good
and then you so you know
you do this like normal
like you're doing
and then instead of going inside
it's like normal
like you're doing
and then instead of going inside
you see it going inside
oh i want to go
outside oh
and instead of going inside
oh
so that's like this
this the standard
it's like
capacity measure
yeah what you can do is you can sort outside
okay see like that oh
alright
it's funny yeah
cause it
a lot of the time
it looks natural
like considering that there's
still a lot of product on
um this
skills are
alright you know what i've done
i know
i don't know my eyes are closed
you are
trying to do juggling
oh no wait that sounds
that sounds about right
the juggling doctor
juggling professor
yeah juggling professor
yeah i met Kevin on an airplane
we
were sitting beside each other
i was coming back from Canada
and um he had this like big bag
and the airline steward
was like
excuse me sir
your bag's not gonna fit
in the overhead bin
you have to put it underneath
yeah so i grabbed his
laptop from him and i said here
give that to me
and i held
on to it for a second
and then he he like sat down
and then
and we were
sitting right beside each other
so somehow
we just ended up talking
the whole way oh and
i don't know
something just
kind of struck
me that
i was like
i think i like this guy
and i just kind of knew
right away
right there oh
and uh and so then
and i've i've always like
you know i've always wondered
you know if you fly
on an airplane if you'd ever
meet somebody but
sounds like sounds like movie
it was really cute yeah
that's cute
yeah it sounds cute
that's cute story
and then now eye makeup okay
overall
Eyebrows or eyelids
Both are too narrow, so it's a bit
masculine
It was a distinctive eye.
But then I realized
Eyebrows or something
This expression of the eyelids
So that you don’t feel a bit frustrated
Even though
Try to be sexy
I did a lot
Okay um
okay yes the first
i'm using the purple color
the front of the eyelid
dark
I didn't use strong shadows.
It may seem more frustrating
Because it’s snow, if you do something wrong,
Those colors were aimed
It's seventy
strength
and it's interesting the colors
like that that
tone i would have never thought
to use that tone really yeah
ego style
looks like more gifts
for your baby face
okay this is totally different
yes yeah you know the culture
doll like yeah doll like
and baby face
for the perfect dinner time
i'm putting a something
like a portion
it's amazing yeah it's amazing
I'm so good to this person
It suits me 5 my god
Ah, if you turn it like this, it's pink, and if you turn it like this, it's a painting, and it's really pretty. Ah, wow view 5 My Gash 5
My gash is right
oh my god you look like almost
twenty
that's the goal wow
wow
I'll just make it
more than the original lips
I'm drawing it very high.
oh yes it's
it's the lip color is perfect
this is the lips i dream of
oh so pretty
thank you
let's go for a
change outfit okay yeah
you've done a beautiful job
thank you thank you so much
I really appreciate it
thank you so much
lily lily
Haha
If you're still like this, please
I think it would be funny haha
I'm walking
Now the sandwich, now the reserve member, the reserve member
Wase
Reserve member
pretty pretty pretty
pretty
pretty pretty
grow up
Ayu Reddy
DIU NOW
Let's go Let's go
i'm actually gonna be fifty two
the juggling doctor
juggling professor
yeah juggling professor
and so we're gonna go for dinner
tonight
so obviously
I want to look glowy and pretty
and younger
everybody does
Tooruurururururu open
Wow
yes
i just
felt like a whole new person
i think k beauty
is something
that's really exciting for me
and it's a new adventure
agricel
yeah that was that
was something
for me that i thought
was really cute
i've seen it sometimes in images
on Instagram
or on celebrities
but i never
thought i would have worn it
i think it's fun
Yes, actually, I personally
It was pretty, just so so
I really like the feeling I have
just the feeling she got
I felt like it filled me up more.
In reality, your hair looks healthy.
The layers are correct
The bangs details have changed
It kinda looks like her
Feeling young
That I have to give it to you
I got some focus.
Oppa oppa oppa oppa
Haha
Oh so pretty, so pretty, so sexy, so sexy, so pretty
oh my god it's almost like
a do you like it it's amazing
yeah thank you
guys dancing yeah
It's natural
It's a bit natural
Haha
Ah
Oh, I'm speechless
Oh, it hurts
i'm gonna marry this woman
is that like a proposal
Ah yes haha
so good
uh
Be pretty, be pretty, be pretty
Pretty pretty pretty pretty uh
Haha
what are you doing
I can't hear you
This wind is too strong
what are you doing
Oh this
I brought it from Hyeongwoo.
What is this? It’s really pretty.
It folds and I dry it.
This is a dryer. Oh, it's a dryer.
This is
Become a free bolt all over the world
Wind and performance
It's the same as the one used in Korea. It's the same.
I want to think about it, yeah
Okay, the dryer isn't working right now.
Oh, it's not working here.
Hey, it's really salty with me, yeah, it's light.
It's good
I'll stop you first.
After writing this, for now
Please lend me
Okay
Oh, let's go, let's go. It's twenty minutes. Twenty minutes.
let's go let's go
Uh the weather is really nice today uh
It's warm. Yes, the weather is really nice today.
Let's run today too
today
Changhoon noona did my hair, okay?
So Flynn, that's right.
that point
While doing my hair
We usually now
Like miniatures or something like that.
But today
Teacher Changhoon said he was going to apply our cute makeup on the 5th. It was so cute.
Ah yes haha oh yes
Ah, I guess I'm too old.
I'm so cute, cute
why so
Cute expressions like that
I don't use it these days
From now on, I will definitely
I'll call the miniature cute too.
Don't use mini mascara or anything like that.
Cute mascara haha
It's good uh today
Oh, it's cute.
Oh really
But rather, I am a window student.
Words can become popular again now, right?
Cute, cute, kid
Like 2K, yes 5 goes back again.
language
Wow
Well, work hard today too
Put it on
leader
Hello, wow, goodbye, Ariseo.
Hi, we had a good time
Say hello to the shop
hi hello
Hi, I had a good time
Hi zen zen haha zen zen
like we can start again
Today too
Fighting
Mom, what are you doing, really?
Yes, that
thank you so much
Thank you so much baby
Senior, this is lemon colored
I'm impressed. Would you like some?
Good yes
It was so cold yesterday so I did this today
Drink something warm
Yes, I think I should drink it.
Maybe you're a star
Does anyone have the same thing?
now
This is
If you eat two
right away
It will be resolved within today, yes.
yes now yes
I brought it
Oh, what is this? I’m allergic to it.
I'm putting it on right away.
Go sit down
It sinks right away and when something happens, uh
your soul
Wow thank you haha
Hoon, Hoon, make sure to eat this now.
This is Jonghyuk, this is Jonghyuk.
Oh, you must wear this today.
Oh, there's that too, uh, aim for it, uh
It's awesome
Why are you out there?
It's Doraemon too
For Dora Emin
Oh really
Why like this
There's nothing I don't have, I'm Doraemon
I really like Dora Emin
It’s a dragon, so I carry it all with me.
When filming that
That's really clever.
No, because health is best
Oh, that's right, if it hurts
You can't do anything
Get all this ready
Because you came
Yes, you can follow as many times as you like.
You can follow more, just follow along
Either there or hot water
Because I can do that
They say you should drink this in the morning.
Pony, let me find another one.
Sister, thank you for this
I'll eat well, sister.
You can see it, yes
Today is 6 minutes again yes yes tight
I'm going to fill it and the first
Daisy coming
your daisy is 30 today
It's your birthday, so
I'm going to have a surprise party
Now your chocolate while sitting here
Have a cake haha
The sun sets and we all just do it together
You can just do it and get started.
I think so
Could it be that we Koreans
Is this a cake that feels very affectionate? Yes.
That's right, it's good
Yes, yes, that's right, with the leader.
Now today
simply
I received a line or two of feedback.
Please just summarize.
I don't have time
In general, everything is good and good.
I am very good at makeup and skin care
For teaching me
The review said it was very good
How sincerely they treat us
It was really fun to feel like I was giving it to you.
more
I wish they would open a Sol Salon
Oh, I got a little creeped out and
Everyone is so professional
You said it was the same
Yes, what you need to calculate is
uh 10 days
I think the distribution was a bit disappointing.
It keeps coming up
one person one person
The waiting time was a little annoying
a little
It was a long time. Oh right.
Looking at this, it's about delay.
That's us, we're worried too
Customers also give such feedback
This is 10 days
Distribution is a bit
It seems like a problem
The guests lasted three to ten days.
The one sitting here is water
Oh, it's hard
Should I spend some time today?
I think it should be like that, then this time
How many 10 are there now when guiding guests?
How many minutes to finish
If you give it to us, we will now do it too.
continue the time
Put on some makeup while watching
How about doing it?
So just keep making up with this
Well, there are 10 minutes left for Leo’s makeup.
keep me posted
There's another 10 minutes left. Let's talk like this.
Let's communicate with each other.
Uh oh yes
yes hands hands
I think you'll come, leader, leader.
I think you'll come
Decoration, decoration, flower decoration
Fighting today again, today too
Hi cameo hi welcome to general manager hello welcome to general manager
daisy yeah
Nice to meet you
daisy this is my friend Emily
Emily hi Emily
hi daisy i'm Daniel
nice to meet you so have a sit
here
Everyone has to go into the bathroom.
Let's all go in together now
Well, while taking the order
When you receive your order and come in
We stand out so much
us
It's suspicious, then let's make it now
It looks suspicious to anyone
I think I need to make it quickly
Make it here, make it here and then
plate
You don't have to build it on top of it.
Wait a minute, hurry up
You have to tear it apart, plate, plate.
plate where plate plate
I put the plate here.
It's round
It's so small here, one by one
10,000 years 10,000 years
10,000 just like this anyway
But a little too much
It's so, so, so simple, but just
You can't fight
You can't fight about this. Oh, then.
Like this, yes, yes, in this way
It's pretty, but Korea is
Because it’s affection, it’s affection in Korea.
Let's shape the cake
In the shape of a cake
The only thing I can take is to raise the medicine
It's like a little bit of that gift
Can't we fight here?
Now do this
Blow out the candle
no no
here here
Here, this, this, this, this, middle
Broken Broken
Do this and in one
Inside
maybe this banana milk latte
yes that is a very famous thing
you know can i get two of those
two of those
yes thank you so much we
also have
snack menu so
we'll take some snacks okay
so yeah can we get the top two
please okay so maybe one of this
and one of yeah
thank you so much okay thank you
Please return it yes
Something to decorate for 30 seconds
There is nothing
so how are you today
guys good it's my birthday
yeah it's your birthday
oh my gosh
congratulations
thank you so much
i'm excited
we wanted to have like a little
treat myself day so
That's why we came in today
what a coincidence
Listen to everything here. Are you ready?
Oh, it's there too. Did anyone hear it?
There's nothing to brag about
Leo, you will greet me today.
Because you are a guest, you are
I think it would be a good idea to congratulate you
birthday
Congratulations on this
happy birthday
thank you
that's so nice
thank you guys
it was such a good surprise
thank you happy birthday
thank you
daisy are you ready
for the consultation i am
yes please follow me okay
Haha, it was successful.
Haha, I think I like it, really.
It was good, it was good, it was good
So
so welcome to our salon
so nice
so daisy
how are you feeling about your
makeover
i'm excited
very excited
yeah i'm turning 30 today
so i feel like turning 30
yeah it's more special
it's a big one
so i was like started
with a whole new energy yeah
new way of doing my makeup
and new hair
would be start the new decade
fresh you know okay
can i ask for your job yeah
i'm a producer
for a TV
show over here oh really
yeah oh my gosh yeah
i am a freelance
producer for reality TV
i'm an editor associate producer
so i kind of help out
doing the behind the scenes
of reality shows
i
worked for a couple of companies
like Netflix
HBO here in New York
and i was helping out with
bling empire
and real housewives
i'm always
used to being the person
that like gets
so it feels fun
to be like on the other side
oh yeah
you're always
like a supporting side
exactly
i'm always running around
doing all the work so
it's like
it's nice to be spoiled today
being on the other side of it
yeah you're just like a main
lady of the show
today so that's perfect
my name is daisy William
and i'm a producer
for television shows
i'm coming here today
because it's my birthday
i'm turning thirty
and i'm really looking
to get kind of a new look
maybe a little makeover
and just feel really confident
on my birthday today
I love you haha
Mission Live Treatment For You
This is a bit of a difficult mission, but yes, now
There's a lot of tangled hair
It was difficult, it was difficult, yes
Half of the back of my head is tangled like this
So entangled and fluffy like this
If you untangle your hair incorrectly, it will cause hair loss.
I really have to be careful.
We are very sensitive
I will consult with you
I keep doing this
From the bottom, slightly with your teeth
Yes, like ruling a dozen
yeah i want to keep it
oh do you want to
little bit trimmed your hair
yeah i want to keep it long but
definitely
a little bit more shape
okay to it too hmm
i take the earrings
keep your length and then
your smooth connection to your hair
okay do you like this look yeah
i used to have something
closer to
that like the curtain
curtain
You will do it
Yes, but I'm just going to refine it a bit now.
head
Because my hair is all tangled up
I think it will take a while, about 10
10 minutes
Ah, here we go
Ah, but it will be a bit difficult in 30 minutes.
Here it is
Ah, because Teacher Leo is delaying
It's been 10 years
Even if you share it, you have to give it half.
It's okay, the light is like this
No, we have to do more, we have to do more
let's do this together
We have to turn it on together
Yeah
The next person will arrive 30 minutes late.
What should I do?
Candice says you're 30 minutes late.
Candice, it's a 30 minute delay.
ha
I can't do it
Then I get pushed back later.
Hey am so sorry for the lay it is
crazy pony bro
After finishing, I have to put on makeup.
Michele, you have to wait a while.
Oh, it's too 30 minutes late.
What should I do?
Then it's 12 o'clock in total.
Not at half, but at one hour
It looks like I need to put on makeup.
Yeah yeah yeah
But the second and third are a bit
so tight
Now is the time
This is my head
Get a little haircut and this is why
They say it's getting longer.
Because I have to go in at 11:30.
I can finish it by one o'clock
Because I have to deal with the next customer.
Yes, then join me quickly.
Let's finish it, that's it
I think it will get better, that’s right.
Apparently the hair could be shaved
Well, I have to wait a long time again.
Should we share the V?
What are eyebrows and me?
This is the face
Oh just give me directions
Because you are the main one anyway
When to do
Please do something
Do it like this or
the other side
Oh, do you do that on the other side?
It can't be in an absolute position from above.
Two-decker Curving Two-decker
Pore like this
Go to Instagram
Yeah, like this, like this
Like this
Oh your head hey okay like this
tangled hair
Curly hair is especially combed like this.
It has to happen
I have to release it like this.
Lightly, gently, softly
My head is loosening up
s nice
I solved everything later. 5 Well done.
I got cut, yes.
But Leo
The bread needs to come in quickly, Leo.
I have to get in quickly.
Because now it's time to do Leo
Because that Leo too
Yes, that Irina is coming now.
Yes, overlap, overlap
Oh, so quickly
I got hit quickly because I had to change shifts.
You have to do it quickly. They said we would do it together.
If you happen to be here
Do I have to go or
I have to finish it and go here.
within 10 minutes
It's good to go into Leo's room.
Yes, until the next hand comes
You can do it.
When the next hand comes
Wash your hair first
You just have to do your hair first.
It's cool
Listen to Community again, My Rex Good Yes
oh very clean of your hair
yeah looks so good already
she's so much of it
um
Very glossy expression
It worked, but with a highlighter
I expressed it
It looks like this, something like this
snow
Yeah yeah yeah
good
Look at clothes, yeah
Now, Teacher Leo, come in.
hi hi
come here and sit please daisy
thank you sit
thank you
Nice to meet you
lovely to meet you yeah
are you feel good today i do
i saw your dress
yeah yeah it's so pretty
thank you so much
we're going on a boat
like a little
sail yacht
sailing around yeah wow
it's like a little yacht thing
yeah so i
felt like it was blue and white
felt like
nautical
but still cute and birthday
right
thank you for coming
with your special day right
thanks for making me pretty
for my boat
so you can all come on the boat
tonight we
hope we hope to go there
so much yeah
but
many customers going to come
right
sorry can i have
the shave your eyebrow
yes i would love that actually
thank you
please thank you
지금 들어갈 거 같은데
don't you know
we got the world
we got the bottle lecture i got the juice
down oh
we got the bottle lecture
i got the juice
we got
the bottle lecture i got the juice i love it so much i love it
we got the bottle lecture
I folded it up.
I caught it here. It's a little clean.
My hands are older
eyeliner here
Can you fill me in? Okay.
Should I make it black or brown? Something like that.
Totally black
All skin blemishes were covered.
Thank you sir, oh my dad
It doesn't add up
I couldn't help it. My sister was trying to help me too much.
They take care of me a lot, so
He was so good at it
Just think about your work style.
It fits really well. It's pretty.
Oh good
Oh, your eyebrows are pretty. So pretty.
I'm really with Leo
too much work
I want to try it a lot.
do you two work together a lot
like doing makeup
it's the first time
because
you're a really good team
together yeah
you're so close now
yeah
because you're
really famous in Korea so
he is too
i was gonna say you both
should be very very famous
you're both really good
his number one makeup artist in
no stop
okay stop it stop stop
keep going
like i don't want to leave
this is my favorite room now
thank you
Candace is a little late.
It was 30 minutes
Oh, I went in.
I'm in, no, not yet
Candace is now 32
um, but he's not coming.
I
Consultation should be done quickly.
I'll send it quickly
So now, a little bit from other things
I need to reduce it.
I should have learned how to shampoo again
I did
Why are you blow drying and blowing hair now?
I should even learn shampoo
This haircut lasted less than an hour
Was there one more person?
So now the delay
Okay, it’s very complicated.
I think it will come
It's difficult
Haha
Hey, really
Isn't it easy?
Using name and reality means
So far, as a guest
We lived comfortably
No complaints from CEO
When am I dissatisfied?
Have you ever talked about the situation?
Find the font now
I have to leave, pony, pony, pony
Oh really
I saw you writing it earlier uh huh
Who are we?
I wrote it to talk behind your back.
I wrote it down haha
And who came here
What did you and Joojong write?
You wrote something strange so I deleted it.
I changed it to cool
I changed it but who
I still don't know if I wrote it
older sister
This is just buried
Okay waist waist waist waist up
Oh, I think you're here.
uh
Uh uh uh
thank you
Welcome Hi Candy
Welcome to the leader haha
Please come in
The door is closing, the door is closing quickly
We welcome you with a watermelon, Mr.
uh
candy
Uh yes hello 5 hi candy
5 jackpot 5 jackpot 5 jackpot
at first i totally freaked out
because
i am a huge k drama fan yeah
he set my computer
from the other side of
screen and walking out of it
to be in real life
i was just my mind just
oh my god
sorry i'm cool
nice to meet you sorry i'm cool
nice to meet
you
Oh okay
Ah no hello ah
You're even more surprised now haha
Oh, are you Korean?
Oh really
You can sit here. Yes.
But you're better than Korean people.
Haha, you said it was awesome, awesome haha
Please come this way. Thank you.
sorry
i'm so sorry for being late
um so sorry i'm so sorry
oh my god
okay so let’s go to
consultation room first yes
yes okay
um is this is
Are you so surprised? There is no information.
Now that I see people I know
I'm excited ah
many people say yes
Ah, that Korean actor
I'm working as an actor and maybe K.
A lot of dramas
I guess it's because I saw it, yeah
For some reason, you look so pretty haha
Eh
They are all actors and they are really in there.
Because there are experts
I think I know because I've already heard it.
My name is Ramiran haha
Oh, it's so pretty you won't recognize me
Ah ah pretty
Oh please say yes haha
Sorry haha
I have a lot more. Oh yeah.
I went on a diet haha
It's not like that in the first place
Haha ah
Because there is no TV at home these days.
Don't watch TV
Ah why like this
I wondered if it was surprising. Oh, it was true.
Really ahaha
stunned
so this is real life
this is real
this is real this is okay
you didn't know that
i don't have any idea
do you have no but it told me
yes so my roommate told me
about this
like he beauty salon yeah
and then she said
you should totally try it
she said
yeah you would
love it
you always
wanted to make a difference you
always wanted to make a change
for yourself
so
can i ask for your job
yes i work for the public sector
work at the un
yeah
well that's cool yeah
i'll do that yeah okay
i just graduated
from Columbia university
studying global policy
and management
and
international security policy
currently
working in the public sector
at the un
i'm very glad i'm very
glad to you know having you
like a with a big reaction
okay before we start
do you have any
allergies or concerns
about your skin
oh acne acne yeah acne scar
my hair is pretty long right now
so you have a lot of
layers there yeah
what about like a haircut or
yes
whatever you think is the best
okay
yeah and and i love
k beauty i think it's like
such a great way to bring out
like your beauty
from like the most soft
and subtle way
so well it's so natural
yeah it's so natural yes
and i love things
that are natural
aloha everyone
my name is candice from
Honolulu Hawaii
i'm
very interested in trying out
the k beauty style
it might bring you different
opportunities
that's how we make life
more interesting
and to me i feel like life is
more interesting when you
shake things up a little bit
open to new things
and new adventures
okay yeah
there are a lot of
magicians there magic
you know
so don't worry about it
whatever you think it's the best
Yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay
so i think we're ready
for makeup
oh my god you guys are
Oh, I'm already preparing
It's so funny
He's my shampoo man. I'll wash your hair.
I learned
Yes, my name is Jonghyuk.
Strange Lawyer Woo Young-Woo
dry mossu gun
You won't recognize me like this, no no
What kind of life do you live?
your energy is so nice thank you
oh this is crazy
Will that tension last all day?
Ah
wow continue
5 5 nice nice
i will do my best
alright
thank you
no you're already the best
i trust you
that looks so good
oh my god that looks
so good that product is magic
like this
liquid glitter so pretty
so pretty
허 예쁘다
oh that's so pretty
i think it
keeps just getting better
i keep getting more excited
yeah getting better
i'm like it's perfect
that i'm like it keeps
getting more perfect yes
first day
ㅎㅎ
get your workout in
she was
she was strong
i didn't i didn't know that
what are you doing
wow like this
oh my god look at this yeah
so much liquid
oh
another tip
One two three haha
you looked above
Oh yes you are on top
Do it below
Can you take it? There are 30 minutes left.
I'm leaving in 1 minute
1 minute later
My sister helped me a lot
It was over quickly
This person guessed almost 10 times and was perfect.
It's possible all the time
I'm leaving in 1 minute
It's pretty, sir.
Thank you, teacher
This is much more correct. Uh, the lid.
Here it is, yes
Thank you, Somas, thank you, thank you
Hmm
Days Is Coming
yes daisy comes out
Okay 5 haha
yeah i'm turning thirty today so
i feel like i'm
turning thirty yeah
my hair and makeup
i don't really put much effort
into it
i'm coming here today
because it's my birthday
i'm turning thirty
really feeling a bit more glam
and getting some tips
and tricks
is what i was looking for today
와우 와우 오케이
와우 하하하하
you have a blue point
in your dress so i will
add a blue point
in front here
that's so pretty
i feel like a new person
i just died a little bit
and then came back to life
i think it's the best
i've ever lived on my birthday
i would come back
and do this experience
a hundred times over
birthday girl
happy birthday so pretty
your hair looks how cute is it
oh my god look at my makeup
it's so pretty
it's so nice isn't it
oh my god
i keep looking at myself
i'm just like yeah
that's me
right how cute are they
they did a good job yeah
you know i got lash
how cute is that
thank you
so let's go on the boat
they did such a good job
thank you
it's his birthday
it's my birthday
thank you
let's take a photo together
right yeah
yeah
으
으 안 가
ㅎㅎ
yeah got the show
thank you so much
yeah thank you guys so much
it's been the best birthday ever
i feel so pretty
and i can go on to the next like
start work it will come with us
thank you so much
thank you
thank you thank you okay
빠이 가이
안녕히 가세요 빠이 가이 빠이
ㅎㅎㅎ
Wow, your hair is so thick.
There are a lot haha go up
I keep the rings
then this
your hair
line is very heavy and this hair
is very skinny
so and i check the balance okay
cutting is here
sure oh yes
here okay yes it's not shorter
not shorter
i do you want to have shorter hair
sure
ah really yeah yeah i'm okay
yeah
ah it's a big change big
change okay
Oh, do you want to cut your hair a lot?
I tried to refine it, but it kept happening
What are you doing with this?
When originally consulting, Minyoung
With the mayor
I came out because they said they would polish it.
I'll show you some drafts.
One of them is K Style.
I was obsessed with that thing called bead cut.
So that
He asked me to cut his hair.
and
It's not about getting your hair done.
Completely new
It was my head, but I
I don't have time
My hair was this thick.
Heckerling 5 5 5 yes
Hahaha
5 it is
I am I am
i am i
i was super shocked i feel like
i thought i was ready
but when you see it
like that's
like in front of your eyes
and i was like
oh my god that's the change
that i'm making
okay nervous but i was excited
a lot lighter
it felt a lot lighter
Yes, count the candy. There are 30 minutes left.
Could it be that
Because there is a lot of delay
Is it happening now?
Ah, this will take a while.
It's long, hard in this house
It's like a seat
진짜 많다
우리 공격
that that those are all mine
yeah wow
you wanna take it
whoa
wow
it's very light so light yeah
oh i like it i'm liking
it it's a real real hair okay
매직길 한 번만
일단
메이크업실로 갈게요
스타플레이스
뭐해
흠
almost k style yes but i wonder
actress or k pop star
which one is your
more preferred look
are they different
yes it's totally different
yeah because the actress look
more yeah clear and simple
and for everyday makeup yeah
but the kpop
makeup is more like me
yeah the bold lashes
and pop blush
and the more
yeah it's kind of different
So a little more than me
I think you can do it in a fancy way.
A little bit deadlier than me
oh really
k idol style yeah okay
you know what's okay
yeah i'll trust you
yeah don't
Yeah yeah yeah
i don't trust myself
but i'll trust you
Oh, sir, can you please give me 10 years?
How about 10 days? Eat something.
Hey there
What should I do if the two of us can't eat?
Oh thank you so much
For doing it well
There are a lot of people who didn't eat today.
Ugh no
We couldn't eat, so come back to work.
Yes, yes
Eat quickly while you’re in there.
Ah, Mr. Jonghyuk
You had a hard time today. Yes, no.
No, CEO, that pin earlier.
Thank you so much to the server. Grab this.
giving
No, usually
My head looks like this
In many cases, it requires a little bit of refinement.
You're so pretty
I think it matches well with the outfit.
I want to do something artistic
uh
How are you?
Not 50
um
But today was hard
It's not over yet
Today must have been difficult
What is there
Ah, time is running out.
Oh right, I'm sorry
What is there to do?
Oh my, I am so
Because it's not that kind of problem
I know
No, the ending is imminent.
I didn't do it because of the sun, yeah
I said yes
Suddenly, I got twisted two miles and got hit.
Yeah, it's because of me
No
Because I'm not a teacher
Why do you keep saying that?
I just like it
No no we
It's not like that, but I eat ramen
Should I eat ramen?
It's a bit lacking
eat it no
Is it okay? Is it okay? Yes.
I want to eat, okay, okay.
Yes I am
When you're tired
You shouldn't eat spicy food
Isn't it?
Exploit it together
Go to the temple, go to the temple
Oh, I'm sorry. That's what that guy said.
This is an occupational disease, so
I work at a hair salon base.
Because time is so important
Because then
These people have schedules.
Because there is a delay, this
The pressure is really big.
There will be a lot of delay.
I can do it
You can do it, eye candy
Good luck, teacher!
Cheer up haha
I need to eat this as a snack
I have a good idea after eating this
Yes, and you should eat bananas too.
I'm going to eat it all. Eat it all.
Don't stop me, I won't stop you, yeah
Have you eaten everything?
thank you
crazy
i'm moving to Korea after today
Oh, Candice will be here soon.
My friend usually
I did it in a very different style.
Yes uh now
They say you can cover your eyes now uh ah ha
Oh, please cover your eyes. It's okay.
curve 6 ice
my name is candace just
graduated
from Columbia University and
currently
working in the public sector
at the un
i'm learning to beat myself
and to do things
that's good for me as well
so i was talking
to my roommate
about it and she's also Korean
and she was recommending
this place
i'm very interested
in trying out
the k beauty style
Wow
yes
Wow wow
Wow wow wow wow
my god
i'm gonna draw some
eyelashes
Eyes that look like lipstick are wide like this
It had the effect of floating.
we're gonna try
some color
contacts okay
it's just like a
pineapple it's like a oh right
right it looks so
natural right yeah
it's so natural
wow
oh
so pretty
your eyes look bigger
and kind of like a
mysterious feeling
you know
There's a K style, it's called a bead cut.
Wow
What's the problem?
I saw the dress that day and
in a dress
I need to get my hair done again
oh my god that dress
yes
Uh thank you thank you
5 Thank you Guys, thank you haha 5
My God Thank You 5 My God Thank You
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you
I love you I love you
that was crazy
oh baby
thank you so much for reading
That
It's time, but the hair designer said
Really
It's like gold. Ah, yes, I'm glad.
hello
she's on your hair designer okay
nice to meet you do you want to open up yeah i have
pictures for our friends
you want to see yes
so amazing
because of what i said
i planned your
hairstyle and then and then
it's a good idea
and
Ayustdan
Ayustdan Ayustdan Ayustdan
Yes yes haha
I'm a dancer, I'm a dancer, I'm a dancer
what type of dance kpop dance
kpop dance
wow kpop yeah oh nice
really yeah
wow so amazing
i like kpop dance
i was a little nervous
they said a lot that i
i seemed very shy
because
it was a very unfamiliar
environment for me and i think
an unfamiliar
environment
we can get very like
closed off and shy
you know i used to go
dance academy
really to learn
stepping you know stepping
i don't know
no
and i learn highboy
ㅎㅎ
you know this song
oh that's three kids yes
that's class i know it
i love the dance
that's a good dance
is this
here is many high layer yeah
굉장히 똑같이 얘기했는데
my life is very tired
yeah do you understand
yeah because of many
many thoughts many many ways
and many
is an Caird Many People
Ann Manny Manny Plan
yeah because of many
many people super e wow so amazing
i think all my friends are e i'm the only i real yeah you're gonna be tired yes so
so tired
These curly waves are so pretty
I can me too
Wow so very good
The color is so pretty too
Um yo hair
Color is very nice, thank you, yeah
Many Korea Light This Color haha
That's right
Because you understand Korean well
Yes, you've become prettier
dino
You've become prettier
It’s Koreaners Hair Removal This Beautiful
change
Wow
yes
Hahahaha yes
Haha
On the other hand, perfect thank you ah
It's really perfect
Ah
good you
I Nice To Meet 6 Ah
what movie do you like
have you been to New Zealand can you create
the new name
in American for human name
can you recommend me for me
I look like a different person
so obsessed
oh
i think i've never
looked this good
ever
really yeah okay you're ready
yes okay
This
Haha it's too wide
Dou doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo doo
They say they’re leaving. Departing.
open
my name is Ashley i'm
twenty three years old
i am a university student but
i never
really knew how to do it myself
so i wanted
to have this experience
to try it and
just try something new
Lalalalalalalalalalalalal
makeup was pretty different
from what i usually do
it was a little bit
scary at first just
cause i didn't know how i would
feel about it
but i am happy
with how it came out
and it's
made me wanna try new things
This friend's lifestyle
Or clothes you like
But looking at it, it was very
He walked around comfortably.
worth doing often
To show you something like that
It will be much more popular
Haveuhull Igari makeup
5 so pretty 5
no shame you are so shy
i was i was a little nervous
when i came
cause i've never done anything
like this before
but i'm giving you a
the different person at the
character
okay yeah right now the third
okay yeah
Oh, are you making fun of me again? Yes, making fun of me again
Yo Skin S 5 Clean
So So Clean
spot spot spot spot small
You've become prettier
It's Korea you guys
i felt really good
when i came here
and everybody
said things like that
or like complimenting my makeup
or my hair
it made me feel like really
pretty
it was all just so
special to me so it made me feel
less like i was
just getting a haircut
and more like
i was being helped
by people who really cared
just made me happy
wow
oh my god wow you're naked wow
I feel incredible wow
you're naked wow
i feel incredible
wow
so pretty oh
your hair is so nice
oh my god it looks so like
can you do it to me
wow it's magic
magic truly
wait i'll turn around for you
wow
you gotta
bend down too i can't
i can't see that high wow wow
oh thank you so much
wow that's so nice
i love it thank you thank you
i i never
i never do anything
like this special
like for my like
appearance or like
hair or makeup
thank you so much
thank you to everyone
for being so kind and helpful
really appreciate it
this is an amazing experience
i'll never do anything
this cool again
thank you guys
짱
짱 5 어떻게 알아 한국말 잘해요
no bye
that was crazy
what just happened
what just happened they're like
oh that's crazy
Now I'm so embarrassed to start dating
Hmm, I guess I was a little nervous. Oh, and the entry ripples were really great, but it was really lovely.
It was the person who did it.
The eyes
I think you're really good at it.
It has a sharp edge
I really
Real work with Leo
I want to try it a lot.
Everything is pretty when you do it
My sister is really good at doing Sam’s makeup.
look at me
i really love drag
drag art
yeah me too
that's what i wanna do
yeah yeah
you wanna
do i want to get into that
yeah yeah
I really like this makeup. It's great for famous makeup artists to work together.
I think it's the first time I've seen it, one day eye, one two makeup, New York ball drag queen, you're fun, right now haha, it's fun, yes, it's the goal of motherhood in the water, but on top of that, there's dark in front.
It sticks
I keep thinking that I should put on more makeup just like my sister did.
wow
Ah I like it
Really like this
I thought I would try it at the shop
It's so amazing